<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Laura D&#39;Angelo</title>
    <link>https://laura-dangelo.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Laura D&#39;Angelo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://laura-dangelo.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://laura-dangelo.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://laura-dangelo.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a postdoctoral researcher in Statistics at the Department of Economics, Management and Statistics (DEMS) at University of Milano-Bicocca (Milan, Italy), working under the supervision of Prof. Bernardo Nipoti (DEMS, University of Milano-Bicocca). I have received my PhD degree in Statistics at Universiy of Padova (Padova, Italy) in 2022 under the supervision of Prof. Antonio Canale (Department of Statistical Sciences, University of Padova) and Prof. Michele Guindani (Department of Statistics, UCI).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conference presentations</title>
      <link>https://laura-dangelo.github.io/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://laura-dangelo.github.io/talks/</guid>
      <description>Invited talk: &amp;ldquo;Bayesian nonparametric clustering of spatially-referenced spike train data&amp;rdquo;; SIS 2022, Caserta, Italy; June 22 – 24, 2022.
  Discussant at the solicited session &amp;ldquo;Bayesian inference for complex random structures&amp;rdquo;; SIS 2022, Caserta, Italy; June 22 – 24, 2022.
  Contributed talk: &amp;ldquo;Bayesian nonparametric analysis for the detection of spikes in noisy calcium imaging data&amp;rdquo;; JSM 2021; August 8 – 12, 2021.
  Contributed talk: &amp;ldquo;Bayesian nonparametric analysis for the detection of spikes in noisy calcium imaging data&amp;rdquo;; ISBA 2021, June 23 – July 2; 2021.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://laura-dangelo.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://laura-dangelo.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>Department of Economics, Management and Statistics (DEMS) University of Milano-Bicocca Piazza dell’Ateneo Nuovo 1, 20126 Milan Email laura.dangelo@unimib.it </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://laura-dangelo.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://laura-dangelo.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>D’Angelo L. (2022) Bayesian nonparametric clustering of spatially-referenced spike train data, in Book of Short Papers SIS 2022.
  Denti F., D’Angelo L. and Guindani M. (2022) Bayesian approaches for capturing the	heterogeneity of neuroimaging experiments, in Book of Short Papers SIS 2022.
  D&amp;rsquo;Angelo L. (2022) Bayesian modeling of calcium imaging data (PhD Thesis).Supervisor: Prof. Antonio Canale; Co-supervisor: Prof. Michele Guindani. Research Padua Archive, Full text</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>https://laura-dangelo.github.io/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://laura-dangelo.github.io/resume/</guid>
      <description>Current position Postdoctoral researcher at the Department of Economics, Management and Statistics (DEMS), University of Milano-Bicocca. Education PhD student in Statistical Science 10/2018 – 11/2021, University of Padova. Thesis title: Bayesian modeling of calcium imaging data. Supervisor: Prof. Antonio Canale. Co-supervisor: Prof. Michele Guindani. Master’s Degree in Statistics 10/2015 – 11/2017, University of Padova. Thesis title: Modelli Bayesiani nonparametrici: applicazioni al settore assicurativo (Bayesian nonparametric models: applications in insurance).Supervisor: Prof. Antonio Canale.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>